Octavia Lintang Pramesti

SUMMARY

Im Student at the faculty of computer science, Brawijaya University. Have experience in website development, database design, data processing, and ui/ux design. Passionate in activities that require problem solving skills and have an interest in the software engineer profession.

SKILLS

HARD SKILLS

- HTML
- Database design
- CSS
- MySQL
- Laravel
- Java
- Vue is
- Python
- Rest API
- UI design

SOFT SKILLS

- Solution to problem
- Colaboration and teamwork
- Creativity
- · Analytical thinking
- Passionate in education
- Adaptive

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

SMK Negeri 5 Tangerang

Computer Science 2016 - 2019

Brawijaya University

Information Technology GPA 3.72 2020 - now

EXPERIENCE

Virtual Intern: Full Stack Developer BTPN Syariah x Rakamin Academy April 2023 - Mei 2023

 Completing various tasks related to the full stack such as database creation and Rest API that can be utilized by BTPN Syariah.

Computer Lab Assistant (Web Development) Faculty of Computer Science Brawijaya University Februari 2023 - Juni 2023

- Guiding students in understanding website development courses
- Make corrections to student reports in website development courses
- Create a project case to measure the level of understanding and creativity of students in implementing website creation

Data Quality Control PT Amido Makmor Tulus Sejati Juni 2019 – Desember 2019

- Changing medical record physical into digital data
- Ensuring the data format is in accordance with regulatory standards so that it can be processed properly in the next process
- Perform quality control and preprocessing of hospital patient medical record data

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

Team Lead Manager - BIOS Filkom UB Februari 2023 - Now

- Coordinate with division head in FILKOM BIOS to record work program to be executed
- Directing work plans to divisional units so that programs and activities can be carried out effectively and efficiently
- Responsible for division team performance

Head of dance division - BIOS Filkom UB Februari 2023 - Juni 2023

- Lead and coordinate the activities of management staff in carrying out tasks and work programs
- Ensure all activities run according to schedule
- · Create a work program with management staff
- Responsible for the work program that is run

Staff Research and Development KBMTI FILKOM UB (2020)

- Collect materials that can be used as student learning materials
- Helping information technology study program students in preparing for semester exams by holding sinau bareng activities

Secretary - IT Community Agustus 2016 - Mei 2019

- Arrange activity schedules such as work program agendas, workshops, and study together at SMKN 5 Tangerang
- Ensure project activities run according to schedule
- · Write down the results of the discussion for the next activity

Email lintangpramesti77@gmail.com

Github github.com/lintangp

Linked in www.linkedin.com/in/lintang-pramesti-912095201/